Subtitle Provide by dramacool.asia Translator [Admin.@YNG]
تم توفير الترجمة بواسطة مترجم dramacool.asia [Admin.@YNG]
♪When your lies and indifference♪
♪عندما تكذب ولا مبالاتك♪
♪Pierce my heart and shatter it♪
♪اخترق قلبي وحطمه♪
♪All my piety and persistence♪
♪كل تقواي ومثابرتي♪
♪Are torn apart, turning into bubbles in the air♪
♪تتمزق وتتحول إلى فقاعات في الهواء♪
♪When my fairy tale is broken by you♪
♪عندما تحطم حكايتي الخيالية بسببك♪
♪Turning into nightmares that haunt me♪
♪تتحول إلى كوابيس تطاردني♪
♪I decide to break free from your shackles♪
♪قررت أن أتحرر من قيودك♪
♪No longer swallowing the poison apple♪
♪ لم يعد يبتلع تفاحة السم ♪
♪You fed me♪
♪لقد أطعمتني♪
♪I burn the fairy tale, rewrite the role♪
♪أحرق الحكاية الخيالية، وأعيد كتابة الدور♪
♪Reborn as a resolute me♪
♪ولدت من جديد كشخصية حازمة♪
♪I have broken free from your shackles♪
♪لقد تحررت من قيودك♪
♪Throwing away that poison apple♪
♪رمي تلك التفاحة المسمومة♪
♪You fed me♪
♪لقد أطعمتني♪
[Love Conspiracy]
[مؤامرة الحب]
[Adapted from Enhenzhai's novel, Madam, No Mercy for Scum]
[مقتبس من رواية إينهينزهاي، سيدتي، لا رحمة للحثالة]
[Episode 5]
[الحلقة 5]
Song Zhizhi,
أغنية زيزهي،
you actually joined the competition behind my back.
لقد انضممت بالفعل إلى المنافسة دون ظهري.
Dear audience,
عزيزي الجمهور،
after a week of intense deliberation,
بعد أسبوع من المداولات المكثفة،
our panel of judges has selected 100 contestants.
لقد اختارت لجنة التحكيم لدينا 100 متسابق.
[Quefeng Jewelry Competition Heats Up]
[مسابقة مجوهرات كويفنغ تشتد]
They successfully passed the screening round
لقد اجتازوا جولة الفحص بنجاح
and officially advanced to the preliminary round.
وتقدم رسميًا إلى الدور التمهيدي.
The final showdown will take place one week from now.
وستقام المباراة النهائية بعد أسبوع من الآن.
Let's look forward to the moment when the champion is crowned!
دعونا نتطلع إلى اللحظة التي سيتم فيها تتويج البطل!
I just doodled a few lines.
لقد قمت فقط برسم بعض السطور.
How could that qualify as a competition entry?
كيف يمكن أن يكون هذا مؤهلاً للمشاركة في المسابقة؟
You're being too modest.
أنت متواضع للغاية.
Alright. Thank you.
حسناً، شكراً لك.
Mr. Yi,
السيد يي،
why haven't you opened this?
لماذا لم تفتح هذا؟
It's almost as if
إنه تقريبا كما لو
you've expected this outcome.
لقد توقعت هذه النتيجة.
Mr. Yi Wenhan
السيد يي وينهان
is the lead designer at our company.
هو المصمم الرئيسي في شركتنا.
It's only natural for him
إنه أمر طبيعي بالنسبة له
to pass the initial selection.
لاجتياز الاختيار الأولي.
You're right.
أنت على حق.
[Advanced]
[متقدم]
Congratulations, Mr. Yi.
مبروك السيد يي.
We all know that Mr. Yi Wenhan
نحن نعلم جميعا أن السيد يي وين هان
is an accomplished designer with a collection of works.
هو مصمم ماهر لديه مجموعة من الأعمال.
What motivated you
ما الذي حفزك؟
to participate in this competition?
للمشاركة في هذه المسابقة؟
Just to burnish your credentials?
فقط لتلميع بيانات الاعتماد الخاصة بك؟
As everyone knows,
كما يعلم الجميع،
Starlight Jewelry means a lot to me.
مجوهرات ستارلايت تعني الكثير بالنسبة لي.
Jewelry design
تصميم المجوهرات
isn't just a hobby for me.
ليست مجرد هواية بالنسبة لي.
It's my dream.
إنه حلمي.
Over the years,
على مر السنين،
I've helped lead Starlight Jewelry
لقد ساعدت في قيادة شركة Starlight Jewelry
to some encouraging results.
إلى بعض النتائج المشجعة.
And in the future,
وفي المستقبل،
under my management, it will reach
تحت إدارتي، سوف تصل
even greater heights.
ارتفاعات أكبر.
Well said, Mr. Yi.
حسنًا، السيد يي.
We all know
نحن جميعا نعلم
you currently oversee both the design and marketing departments
أنت تشرف حاليًا على كل من أقسام التصميم والتسويق
at Starlight Jewelry.
في مجوهرات ستارلايت.
You're also one
أنت أيضا واحد
of the most influential young designers in the country.
من المصممين الشباب الأكثر تأثيرًا في البلاد.
So
لذا
we can't wait to see you kill it.
نحن لا نستطيع الانتظار لرؤيتك تقتله.
It's also been said
وقد قيل أيضا
that after marrying Ms. Song Zhizhi,
أنه بعد الزواج من السيدة سونغ تشيزي،
you will officially take over as CEO of Starlight Jewelry.
سوف تتولى رسميًا منصب الرئيس التنفيذي لشركة Starlight Jewelry.
We wish you the best of luck.
نتمنى لك التوفيق.
Thank you all for your support.
شكرا لكم جميعا على دعمكم.
I'm not marrying him.
انا لا اتزوجه
Disgusting.
مقزز.
Well, you broke off our engagement for him.
حسنًا، لقد ألغيت خطوبتنا من أجله.
I was blind.
لقد كنت أعمى.
But you have to admit, Yi Wenhan
ولكن عليك أن تعترف، يي وين هان
is quite something.
هو شيء مميز.
I never expected that in just a few years,
لم أتوقع أبدًا أنه في غضون سنوات قليلة،
he'd gain control over all domestic operations
سيحصل على السيطرة على جميع العمليات المحلية
of Starlight Jewelry.
من مجوهرات ستارلايت.
No wonder the profits
لا عجب أن الأرباح
have been plummeting so much in the past few years.
وقد انخفضت بشكل كبير في السنوات القليلة الماضية.
So did you join this competition
فهل انضممت إلى هذه المسابقة؟
because of him?
بسببه؟
I'm using this competition
انا استخدم هذه المنافسة
to earn my way into the design department
لكسب طريقي إلى قسم التصميم
of my dad's company,
من شركة والدي،
become the design director,
أصبح مدير التصميم،
and kick Yi Wenhan out.
وطرد يي وين هان.
Besides,
بجانب،
shouldn't I be
ألا ينبغي لي أن أكون
the designer for our co-branded
المصمم لعلامتنا التجارية المشتركة
high jewelry collection?
مجموعة المجوهرات الراقية؟
You're the Song family's eldest daughter.
أنت الابنة الكبرى لعائلة سونغ .
Is it hard for you to secure the design director position?
هل من الصعب عليك الحصول على منصب مدير التصميم؟
Yes.
نعم.
Getting shares would be easy.
سيكون الحصول على الأسهم أمرًا سهلاً.
But I'm now aiming to infiltrate
ولكنني الآن أهدف إلى التسلل
the company's senior management.
الإدارة العليا للشركة.
I've just realized now.
لقد أدركت ذلك الآن فقط.
Though my family holds the majority stake
على الرغم من أن عائلتي تمتلك حصة الأغلبية
in Starlight Jewelry,
في مجوهرات ستارلايت،
the old-timers on the board
كبار السن على اللوحة
are always sticking their noses into our affairs.
إنهم يتدخلون دائمًا في شؤوننا.
They seem to trust Yi Wenhan more.
يبدو أنهم يثقون في يي وين هان أكثر.
Then strive hard to win this competition.
ثم اجتهد في الفوز بهذه المسابقة.
It's important to me too.
إنه مهم بالنسبة لي أيضاً.
Take care.
يعتني.
Easy does it.
من السهل القيام بذلك.
Mr. Yi is young and promising.
السيد يي شاب واعد.
Young and promising. Truly outstanding.
شاب وواعد. رائع حقًا.
Looks like Yi Wenhan is a shoo-in for the championship.
يبدو أن يي وين هان هو المرشح الأبرز للفوز بالبطولة.
He's already the design director at our company.
وهو بالفعل مدير التصميم في شركتنا.
Winning this will get him a much higher position.
الفوز بهذا سيجعله يحصل على مركز أعلى بكثير.
What's there to be so proud of?
ما الذي يجعلك فخوراً جداً؟
It's all because of his connections to the Songs.
كل هذا بسبب ارتباطاته بالأغاني.
Brother,
أخ،
they know nothing.
لا يعرفون شيئا.
You're the best.
أنت الأفضل.
What do you know?
ماذا تعرف؟
How many times do I have to tell you?
كم مرة يجب أن أخبرك؟
Don't call me that in public.
لا تناديني بهذا في الأماكن العامة.
[Quefeng Jewelry National Design Competition] [Judge]
[ مسابقة تصميم المجوهرات الوطنية في كويفينج] [الحكم]
National Design Competition]
[ مسابقة تصميم المجوهرات الوطنية Quefeng ]
National Design Competition] [Final]
[ مسابقة تصميم المجوهرات الوطنية Quefeng ] [النهائي]
Guanshu, this design is pretty good.
قوانتشو، هذا التصميم جيد جدًا.
Mr. Ye!
السيد يي!
Shan!
شان!
Shan.
شان.
Wishing the competition a great success.
متمنيا للمسابقة النجاح الكبير.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
You must be Baijian, right?
يجب أن تكون بايجيان، أليس كذلك؟
Long time no see.
وقت طويل لا رؤية.
You've grown into quite the impressive young man.
لقد أصبحت شابًا مثيرًا للإعجاب.
Tell me,
أخبرني،
is your dad still upset with me?
هل والدك لا يزال مستاء مني؟
I haven't heard anything about that.
لم اسمع شيئا عن هذا.
But it's no big deal.
ولكن الأمر ليس بالأمر الكبير.
Just differences in business philosophy.
مجرد اختلافات في فلسفة العمل.
All that is ancient history.
كل هذا هو تاريخ قديم.
Shall we take our seats?
هل يجب علينا أن نجلس في مقاعدنا؟
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Good.
جيد.
This is Ye Taiting,
هذا هو يي تايتينغ،
chairman of Starlight Group.
رئيس مجلس إدارة مجموعة ستارلايت.
Starlight Group is a major player.
تعتبر مجموعة ستارلايت لاعباً رئيسياً.
I heard they're even planning to go public.
سمعت أنهم يخططون للظهور للعامة.
What's he doing here?
ماذا يفعل هنا؟
Baijian.
بيجيان.
[Ji Baijian]
[جي بيجيان]
[Song Zhizhi]
[أغنية زيزهي]
[No Network Connection]
[لا يوجد اتصال بالشبكة]
Sorry. The subscriber you've dialed is powered off.
عذراً، المشترك الذي اتصلت به مغلق.
[Song Zhizhi]
[أغنية زيزهي]
Has Song Zhizhi left?
هل غادر سونغ تشيزي؟
[Ji Baijian] Did she oversleep?
[جي بيجيان] هل نامت كثيرًا؟
Is anyone there?
هل هناك أحد؟
Hello?
مرحبًا؟
Mr. Yi, I really admire you.
السيد يي، أنا معجب بك حقًا.
Hope I can learn from you in the future.
آمل أن أتمكن من التعلم منك في المستقبل.
You're too kind.
أنت لطيف للغاية.
Everyone here is a talented designer.
الجميع هنا مصممون موهوبون.
I'd love the opportunity
سأحب هذه الفرصة
to collaborate with you all.
للتعاون معكم جميعا.
Absolutely.
قطعاً.
Everyone, get ready.
الجميع، استعدوا.
Thank you, Mr. Yi.
شكرا لك سيد يي.
[Yin Qin]
[يين تشين]
Hey, Yin Qin.
مهلا، يين تشين.
Hello, Ji.
مرحباً جي.
Something's wrong. Song Zhizhi left early.
هناك خطب ما. غادر سونغ تشيزي مبكرًا.
She should've been there by now.
كان ينبغي لها أن تكون هناك الآن.
Go find her.
اذهب وابحث عنها.
Get her here. The competition is about to start.
أحضروها إلى هنا. المنافسة على وشك أن تبدأ.
Designers, welcome
المصممين، مرحبا بكم
to the Quefeng Jewelry National Design Competition,
إلى مسابقة تصميم المجوهرات الوطنية في كويفينج،
sponsored by Starlight Jewelry
برعاية مجوهرات ستارلايت
and Jihong Group.
ومجموعة جيهونج.
Please take your seats.
الرجاء أخذ مقاعدكم.
The competition begins now.
المنافسة تبدأ الآن.
The theme of this round is First Love.
موضوع هذه الجولة هو الحب الأول.
[First Love]
[الحب الأول]
Everyone,
الجميع،
half the time has passed.
لقد مر نصف الوقت.
Time is running out.
الوقت ينفذ .
Please pick up the pace.
من فضلك إلتقط الوتيرة.
Mr. Yi looks confident.
السيد يي يبدو واثقا.
Seems like he's sure
يبدو أنه متأكد
to win this year's championship.
للفوز ببطولة هذا العام.
Where is she?
أين هي؟
Her car's at the hotel,
سيارتها في الفندق
but she's nowhere to be found.
ولكن لم يتم العثور عليها في أي مكان.
Time's almost up.
لقد انتهى الوقت تقريبا.
How about this?
ماذا عن هذا؟
You go ask the organizers
اذهب واسأل المنظمين
to reschedule for later.
لإعادة جدولة ذلك في وقت لاحق.
Song Zhizhi is from Starlight Group, after all.
سونغ تشيزي هو من مجموعة ستارلايت، بعد كل شيء.
No.
لا.
She's using a pseudonym
إنها تستخدم اسما مستعارا
instead of her real name
بدلا من اسمها الحقيقي
to avoid gossip.
لتجنب النميمة.
I'll check the underground garage.
سأتحقق من المرآب تحت الأرض.
You keep looking around nearby.
تستمر في النظر حولك بالقرب.
Song Zhizhi!
أغنية Zhizhi!
Song Zhizhi.
أغنية زيزهي.
What are you doing? Open the door.
ماذا تفعل؟ افتح الباب.
Song Zhizhi!
أغنية Zhizhi!
I will work with Zhizhi to take Starlight Jewelry
سأعمل مع Zhizhi لأخذ مجوهرات Starlight
to new heights!
إلى آفاق جديدة!
Winning this award
الفوز بهذه الجائزة
is all thanks to my own efforts.
كل هذا بفضل جهودي الخاصة.
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
Is the competition over?
هل انتهت المنافسة؟
Did Yi Wenhan win?
هل فاز يي وينهان؟
What nonsense are you talking about?
ما هذا الهراء الذي تتحدث عنه؟
There's still time.
مازال هناك وقت .
Isn't that Ms. Song?
أليست هذه السيدة سونغ؟
She's only showing up now?
هل ظهرت الآن فقط؟
Zhizhi, what are you doing here?
زيزي، ماذا تفعل هنا؟
I'm Enna.
انا إينا.
I'm here to compete.
أنا هنا للتنافس.
But there are
ولكن هناك
less than 30 minutes left.
بقي أقل من 30 دقيقة.
You can't possibly finish in time.
من غير الممكن أن تنتهي في الوقت المحدد.
Who says I can't?
من قال أنني لا أستطيع؟
You're late.
لقد تأخرت.
You're disqualified.
لقد تم استبعادك.
Exactly.
بالضبط.
Just because your family holds the competition?
فقط لأن عائلتك هي من تتولى المنافسة؟
[Time remaining: 29:54]
[الوقت المتبقي: 29:54]
According to the rules,
وفقا للقواعد،
as long as the contestant arrives and completes their work
طالما وصل المتسابق وأكمل عمله
within the allotted time,
في الوقت المحدد،
their entry remains valid.
تظل دخولهم صالحة.
Miss, let her begin.
آنسة، دعيها تبدأ.
Three, two, one.
ثلاثة، اثنان، واحد.
Time's up.
لقد إنتهى الوقت.
The competition is over.
لقد انتهت المنافسة.
Thank you, everyone.
شكرا للجميع.
Once the hostesses
بمجرد أن المضيفات
have collected all the entries,
لقد جمعت كل الإدخالات،
the works of all the contestants
أعمال جميع المتسابقين
will be displayed
سيتم عرضها
on the screen.
على الشاشة.
What we're seeing now
ما نراه الآن
are all 25 pieces of work
كلها 25 قطعة عمل
from every contestant.
من كل متسابق.
We'll have the judges give their scores
سوف نطلب من الحكام إعطاء درجاتهم
and cast their votes.
وأدلوا بأصواتهم.
So, who will the judges
إذن من سيكون القضاة؟
cast their votes for?
يدلون بأصواتهم ل؟
We're all eager to find out.
نحن جميعا حريصون على معرفة ذلك.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
[Contestant: Enna, Votes: 562] [Contestant: Yi Wenhan, Votes: 562]
[المتسابقة: إينا، الأصوات: 562] [المتسابقة: يي وينهان، الأصوات: 562]
The results are in.
النتائج موجودة.
Two designers
مصممين اثنين
have received the same number of votes.
وقد حصلوا على نفس عدد الأصوات.
They are Enna
إنهم إينا
and Yi Wenhan!
ويي وينهان!
Give it up for them!
استسلم لهم!
Congratulations to you both.
مبروك لكما.
Now,
الآن،
we'll turn it over to our judges
سوف نترك الأمر لقضاتنا
to determine the winner.
لتحديد الفائز.
How is a tie even possible?
كيف يمكن أن يكون التعادل ممكنا؟
You're clearly with Starlight Jewelry.
من الواضح أنك مع Starlight Jewelry.
Did you
هل فعلت؟
rig the theme in advance?
تجهيز الموضوع مسبقًا؟
I'll expose you!
سأفضحكم!
Stop making such accusations!
توقفوا عن توجيه مثل هذه الإتهامات!
Anyone with half a brain can see
أي شخص لديه نصف دماغ يمكنه أن يرى
Ms. Song's design is on another level
تصميم السيدة سونغ على مستوى آخر
compared to Yi Wenhan's!
بالمقارنة مع يي وينهان!
It even rivals Anne's.
إنه ينافس حتى آن.
Fine, Song Zhizhi.
بخير، سونغ زيزهي.
Since I can't win...
لأنني لا أستطيع الفوز...
No need to vote!
لا حاجة للتصويت!
Zhizhi,
تشيزي،
since you want this championship this badly,
بما أنك تريد هذه البطولة بشدة،
I'll let you have it.
سأترك لك ذلك.
After all, I know
بعد كل شيء، أنا أعلم
how rigged these competitions can be.
كيف يمكن أن تكون هذه المسابقات مزورة.
I don't care about winning.
لا يهمني الفوز.
All I care about is you.
كل ما أهتم به هو أنت.
You're letting me have it?
هل تسمح لي بالحصول عليه؟
Rigged?
مُزوَّر؟
Have you forgotten?
هل نسيت؟
You plagiarized my work in the preliminary round!
لقد سرقت عملي في الجولة التمهيدية!
Without me,
بدوني،
you wouldn't even have qualified for the competition.
لن تتأهل حتى للمنافسة.
Everyone, look at the screen.
الجميع، انظروا إلى الشاشة.
On the left
على اليسار
is my work from high school.
هذا عملي من المدرسة الثانوية.
On the right
على اليمين
is Mr. Yi Wenhan's entry from the preliminary round.
وهذا دخول السيد يي وين هان من الجولة التمهيدية.
The resemblance is obvious, isn't it?
الشبه واضح، أليس كذلك؟
This has to be rigged.
يجب أن يتم تزوير هذا.
Zhizhi.
تشيزهي.
Stop making a scene.
توقف عن إثارة المشهد.
And there's another thing.
وهناك شيء آخر.
All of Mr. Yi Wenhan's previous works
جميع أعمال السيد يي وين هان السابقة
were actually ghost designed by others.
تم تصميمها في الواقع بواسطة أشباح من قبل آخرين.
I've been in a deal with Mr. Yi Wenhan
لقد كنت في صفقة مع السيد يي وين هان
for five years.
لمدة خمس سنوات.
Back then, my mother was seriously ill
في ذلك الوقت كانت والدتي مريضة بشكل خطير
and I needed money.
وكنت بحاجة إلى المال.
These are all my designs.
هذه كلها تصميماتي.
Here's my
هنا بلدي
copyright registration certificate.
شهادة تسجيل حقوق النشر.
And these
وهذه
are the copyright transfer agreements
هي اتفاقيات نقل حقوق النشر
from when Yi Wenhan bought my works.
منذ أن اشترى يي وين هان أعمالي.
He published them
لقد نشرها
as his own.
كأنها ملكه.
You're framing me!
أنت تؤطرني!
You're making things up!
أنت تصنع أشياء!
You copied the works and hired the ghost designer.
لقد قمت بنسخ الأعمال واستأجرت المصمم الشبح.
What does any of that have to do with me?
ما علاقة كل هذا بي؟
Yi Wenhan,
يي وينهان,
we've treated you well.
لقد عاملناك بشكل جيد.
How could you be so morally bankrupt?
كيف يمكنك أن تكون مفلسًا أخلاقيًا إلى هذه الدرجة؟
From now on,
من الآن فصاعدا،
Yi Wenhan is disqualified from the competition
تم استبعاد يي وين هان من المنافسة
and suspended from all duties at the company!
وتم إيقافه عن العمل في الشركة!
He'll wait for further investigation!
سوف ينتظر المزيد من التحقيق!
Song Zhizhi...
أغنية زيزهي...
Let go of me. Let go!
دعني أذهب. دعني أذهب!
Song Zhizhi set me up.
سونغ تشيزي هيأ لي الأمر.
Yeah, I saw everything.
نعم، لقد رأيت كل شيء.
I'm hanging up.
أنا أعلق.
Hello?
مرحبًا؟
I thought you had arranged for Wenhan to win?
اعتقدت أنك رتبت لفوز وينهان؟
But we didn't expect Song Zhizhi
ولكننا لم نتوقع سونغ تشيزي
to join the competition or get hold
للانضمام إلى المسابقة أو الحصول على
of the evidence that Wenhan plagiarized.
من الأدلة التي تثبت أن وينهان سرق.
You said she wasn't that clever.
لقد قلت أنها ليست ذكية إلى هذا الحد.
That was before.
كان ذلك من قبل.
After Xiaofei's birthday,
بعد عيد ميلاد شياوفي،
I felt she'd changed somehow.
شعرت أنها تغيرت بطريقة ما.
Do you need me to do anything?
هل تريدني أن أفعل أي شيء؟
Look into it thoroughly.
أنظر إلى الأمر جيدا.
I've been taking care of my little flower for years,
لقد كنت أعتني بزهرتي الصغيرة لسنوات،
and now it suddenly wants to bloom and grow its own way?
والآن فجأة يريد أن يزدهر وينمو بطريقته الخاصة؟
I won't allow it.
لن اسمح بذلك
Song Zhizhi.
أغنية زيزهي.
Since you refuse to behave,
بما أنك ترفض التصرف بشكل لائق،
don't blame me for what happens next.
لا تلومني على ما سيحدث بعد ذلك.
Mom.
أم.
Mom, look, it's Song Zhizhi.
أمي، انظري، إنه سونغ تشيزي.
She's really with Baijian?
هل هي حقا مع بايجيان؟
Be quiet.
كن هادئاً.
Read the room.
اقرأ الغرفة.
Get a grip.
سيطر على الموقف.
I'm going over.
سأذهب إلى هناك.
Aunt Wenzhi.
العمة وينزي.
Xiaofei.
شياوفي.
Zhizhi,
تشيزي،
why did you come with Baijian?
لماذا أتيت مع بايجيان؟
I wanted to surprise everyone.
أردت أن أفاجئ الجميع.
I never realized
لم ادرك ذلك ابدا
how exceptional Baijian is.
كم هو استثنائي بايجيان.
So,
لذا،
do you like this surprise?
هل تعجبك هذه المفاجأة؟
Love it.
أحبها.
You're adorable.
أنت رائعه.
You taught me well.
لقد علمتني جيدا.
Yi Wenhan
يي وينهان
is such a scumbag.
إنه مثل هذا الحقير.
Can't believe I actually loved him.
لا أستطيع أن أصدق أنني أحببته فعلاً.
What kind of mother
أي نوع من الأم
raises a son like that?
يربي ابنا مثل هذا؟
Well, Aunt Wenzhi, Xiaofei,
حسنًا، عمتي وينزي، شياو في،
you two carry on. I'm going back over.
استمروا. سأعود.
Okay.
تمام.
Look at her. What's there to be so proud of?
انظروا إليها. ما الذي يدعوها إلى كل هذا الفخر؟
You couldn't pull it off.
لم تتمكن من القيام بذلك.
Don't blame others for being stronger.
لا تلوم الآخرين لكونهم أقوى.
Men don't like whiners.
الرجال لا يحبون المتذمرين
Good evening,
مساء الخير،
everyone.
الجميع.
First, on behalf of Starlight Jewelry and Jihong Group,
أولاً، بالنيابة عن Starlight Jewelry ومجموعة Jihong،
I'd like to thank all of you
وأود أن أشكركم جميعا
for joining us at this gathering!
لانضمامكم إلينا في هذا التجمع!
Besides,
بجانب،
the champion of the competition
بطل المسابقة
is my eldest daughter, Song Zhizhi!
هي ابنتي الكبرى، سونغ تشيزي!
I hereby announce
أعلن بموجب هذا
that Zhizhi
أن Zhizhi
will be joining the design department of Starlight Jewelry!
سوف ينضم إلى قسم التصميم في Starlight Jewelry!
I hope she'll have your support.
آمل أن تحظى بدعمك.
Song Zhizhi's win was rigged!
فوز سونغ تشيزي كان مزوراً!
Let go!
اتركه!
It was rigged!
لقد تم تزويرها!
Let go of me! Let go!
دعني أذهب! دعني أذهب!
Yi Wenhan!
يي وينهان!
This is not the place for your nonsense!
هذا ليس المكان المناسب لهراءك!
Take him away!
خذه بعيدا!
Dad,
أب،
if you do that, everyone will just think I'm guilty.
إذا فعلت ذلك، فسيعتقد الجميع أنني مذنب.
I have nothing to hide.
ليس لدي ما أخفيه.
Yi Wenhan,
يي وينهان,
let's hear
دعونا نسمع
what you have to say.
ما لديك لتقوله.
Everyone!
الجميع!
I have something shocking
عندي شيء صادم
to share with everyone.
لمشاركتها مع الجميع.
The one who accused me, Song Zhizhi,
الذي اتهمني هو سونغ تشي تشي،
is the real plagiarist.
هو السارق الحقيقي.
On the left
على اليسار
is Song Zhizhi's entry for this competition.
هذه هي مشاركة Song Zhizhi في هذه المسابقة.
On the right
على اليمين
is a sketch titled "First Love"
هو رسم بعنوان "الحب الأول"
posted by international jewelry design rising star Anne
نُشر بواسطة نجمة تصميم المجوهرات العالمية الصاعدة آن
on her personal page.
على صفحتها الشخصية.
The two are 70 percent identical!
كلاهما متماثلان بنسبة 70 بالمائة!
Mr. Yi.
السيد يي.
You've got quite the eye.
لديك عين جميلة.
You accuse me of plagiarism based on one piece?
هل تتهمني بالسرقة الأدبية بناء على قطعة واحدة؟
Then let me ask you,
إذن دعني أسألك،
as a plagiarist yourself,
باعتبارك سارقًا أدبيًا بنفسك،
what right or credibility
ما هو الحق أو المصداقية
do you have to question me?
هل تريد أن تسألني؟
I knew
انا عرفت
someone as dishonest as Song Zhizhi
شخص غير أمين مثل سونغ تشي تشي
would deny it
سوف ينكر ذلك
and even try to pin it on me.
وحتى محاولة إلقاء اللوم علي.
That's why
لهذا السبب
I brought Anne's original hand-drawn sketches.
لقد أحضرت الرسومات الأصلية المرسومة يدوياً لآن.
Compare them,
قارنهم
and you'll know
وسوف تعرف
everything I've said is true.
كل ما قلته صحيح.
Here.
هنا.
You even forged something like this?
هل قمت بتزوير شيء مثل هذا؟
Why are these sketches real?
لماذا هذه الرسومات حقيقية؟
[Pendant]
[خلال]
How did you get these sketches?
كيف حصلت على هذه الرسومات؟
Anne gave them to me herself, of course.
لقد أعطتني آن هذه الأشياء بنفسها، بالطبع.
Impossible!
مستحيل!
Because I am Anne.
لأني آن.
You're Anne?
أنت آن؟
I was going to spare you some dignity.
كنت أريد أن أحفظ لك بعض الكرامة.
But since you have no shame,
ولكن بما أنك لا تشعر بالخجل،
I won't hold back.
لن أتراجع.
I've got
لقد حصلت
a surprise for you.
مفاجأة لك.
Let's welcome Anne!
دعونا نرحب بآن!
♪From this moment on, I no longer care♪
♪من هذه اللحظة فصاعدا، لم أعد أهتم♪
♪No more noise in my ears♪
♪لا مزيد من الضوضاء في أذني♪
♪That's the peace I've always yearned for♪
♪هذا هو السلام الذي كنت أشتاق إليه دائمًا♪
♪Who was I trying to change for?♪
♪من كنت أحاول التغيير من أجله؟♪
♪Smiling, crying, complaining♪
♪يبتسم، يبكي، يشكو♪
♪That's the contentment I should learn to embrace♪
♪هذا هو الرضا الذي يجب أن أتعلم احتضانه♪
♪Honestly, I don't care♪
♪ بصراحة، لا يهمني ♪
♪How many times you've hurt me♪
♪كم مرة جرحتني♪
♪What you call sincere devotion♪
♪ما تسميه التفاني الصادق♪
♪Maybe I've just grown numb♪
♪ربما أصبحت مخدرًا للتو♪
♪Honestly, I don't care♪
♪ بصراحة، لا يهمني ♪
♪Even if I've strayed♪
♪حتى لو ضللت الطريق♪
♪I'm still crying for someone♪
♪مازلت أبكي من أجل شخص ما♪
♪Crying over losing to my own pride♪
♪ البكاء على الخسارة أمام كبريائي ♪